<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on KohlerZ</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on KohlerZ</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mock Mars Rover!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/wisconsin-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/wisconsin-robotics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;wisconsin-robotics---2021-2025&#34;&gt;Wisconsin Robotics - 2021-2025&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was heavily involved in Wisconsin Robotics starting at my first semester in UW-Madison. I started on the electrical team as one of the few members, and had to get myself aquainted with the team and its practices very quickly. I had already learned Autodesk EAGLE, so I was able to look at some of the designs of the boards that the graduated students had made for the rover as it stood.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5kW / 3kW Dynamometer for Yaskawa</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/yaskawa-dyne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/yaskawa-dyne/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During my time as a student engineering Co-Op at Yaskawa, my main project was the upgrade of an old 1.5kW dynamometer to use the newest technology and be up to date with the rest of the lab. During the discovery phase, I realized that enabling the dynamometer to run at 3kW would not be too much of a cost barrier and would make sense for the workflow of the team. My supervisors gave me the go-ahead to proceed and I got to work in SOLIDWORKS designing all of the mechanical portions of the test stand.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Jeopardy Buzzer!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/jeopardy-buzzer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/jeopardy-buzzer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-for-platteville-high-school&#34;&gt;Project for Platteville High School&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My physics professor propositioned me and a friend to make this device that could be reliable enough and easy to use for my high-school&amp;rsquo;s pep rallies and assemblies&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the time I had been working more and more with my 3D printer, so I took on the challenge and designed the mechanical and electrical aspects of the device. I used ethernet jacks with crimp connectors to ensure there was little chance of solder joints decaying over time. The ethernet jacks were used to connect to the main hub which contained an arduino to do all the processing. The device was simple to use and started the sequence as soon as power was applied.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
